[Music]
[音乐]
so yeah first of all thanks all for
是的，首先感谢大家
coming to this talk I know there I have
来参加这个演讲，我知道我有
some strong competition I think your
我认为您的竞争很激烈
inhaler is that when at the auditorium
吸入器是在礼堂时
and so yeah I'm going to talk a little
所以，我要谈一点
bit about cloud platforms today or like
关于今天的云平台或类似的东西
platforms that you can use to deploy
可用于部署的平台
your spring mood micro-services so this
您的春季心情微服务，所以这
is not really an in-depth talk about
并不是真正的深入讨论
spring boot or spring technology this is
spring boot 或弹簧技术，这是
more about the deployment and runtime of
有关以下内容的部署和运行时的更多信息
those components my name is Matthias
这些成分我叫马蒂亚斯
this is this is my twitter handle i'm
这是我的推特手柄
using this quite actively so i'm always
非常积极地使用这个，所以我总是
happy
快乐
if i get new followers and get
如果我得到新的追随者并得到
inspiration for people to follow so
人们遵循的灵感
that's me in two different versions so
那是我的两个不同版本
the one to the left is the Cloud Foundry
左边的是Cloud Foundry
ambassador and meetup organizer version
大使和聚会组织者版本
so I am organizing the Cloud Foundry
所以我正在组织Cloud Foundry
meetup that user community in the area
聚集该地区的用户社区
of Stuttgart in Germany so is there
德国斯图加特的地图
anybody from southern Germany in the
来自德国南部的任何人
room okay
房间还好
there's a meet-up next week and you're
下周有个聚会，你
all invited for the ones who are close
所有被邀请参加的人
enough feel free to come by and if I'm
有足够的自由来，如果我是
not doing things on Cloud Foundry
不在Cloud Foundry上做事
kubernetes or the platforms in or for
kubernetes或其中的平台
community works I have a regular day job
社区工作我有固定的日常工作
as a consultant in a company called Nova
作为一家名为Nova的公司的顾问
Tech where I try to help clients getting
我试图帮助客户获取技术的地方
their workloads to the cloud in either
将他们的工作负载转移到云端
like new implementations or migrations
例如新的实现或迁移
and advise them on their on their
并就他们的建议给他们
strategy so speaking briefly about Nova
策略，所以简要谈一下Nova
Tech we mostly operate out of Germany
我们主要在德国以外运营的技术
and we have about 250 to 300
我们大约有250到300
employ years it's mostly around software
雇用多年主要是围绕软件
development modern self development
发展现代自我发展
agile methodologies and everything that
敏捷方法论以及一切
surrounds that
包围
including of course the cloud native
当然包括云原生
aspect so I edit this slide yesterday
方面，所以我昨天编辑了这张幻灯片
and try to highlight that we also have a
并尝试强调我们也有一个
branch in Spain in Granada now on the
现在在西班牙格拉纳达开设分公司
keynote this morning I learned there are
今天早上我做了主题演讲
more German people than Spanish people
德国人多于西班牙人
in the conference so I could highlight
在会议上，我可以强调
all the others as well in general return
所有其他人以及一般回报
based but the Spanish branch is
总部，但西班牙分公司是
increasing so if you have any if you
增加，如果有的话
want any more information about what
想要更多有关什么的信息
we're doing and where we're doing that
我们正在做的事情以及我们正在做的事情
feel free to ping me afterwards so now I
以后随时可以ping我，现在我
don't really want to get in too much
真的不想进得太多
detail about where we're located so I'm
有关我们所处位置的详细信息
gonna give a bit of an intro to kind of
会给一些介绍
frame the talk and tell you what I
讲故事并告诉你我的意思
intend to show so I'm pretty sure most
打算演出，所以我很确定
of you have seen kind of an cloud
你们当中有人看过云
abstraction layer diagram in one or the
一个或多个抽象层图
other form what I wanted to show with
我想展示的其他形式
this is just basically what are the
这基本上是什么
various layers where you can put your
可以放置您的各个层次
software your workloads and what kind
用软件来处理您的工作负载以及什么样的工作
what are the kind of differences so it
有什么区别呢
started off with virtual machines then
从虚拟机开始
they came containers nowadays functions
他们今天来集装箱
or the term server less is used very
或“少用服务器”一词非常常用
frequently basically there's a certain
通常，基本上有
tendency that the work the further you
倾向于工作越远
go down in this tag size a footprint of
缩小标签尺寸
your workloads and and the
您的工作量和
infrastructure increases you have to
基础设施增加，您必须
pick a start up time and tighter
选择启动时间并更紧凑
coupling and cohesion the further you go
耦合和凝聚力越远
up in the stack there's more abstraction
堆栈中有更多抽象
flexibility and distribution of your of
您的灵活性和分布
your services now I'm not going to talk
您的服务，我现在不谈
much about virtual machines and
关于虚拟机和
functions today so I'm gonna stick kind
今天可以运作，所以我会坚持下去
of to container and application layer
到容器和应用程序层
and in order to to demonstrate that how
为了证明这一点
I can deploy and run Springwood
我可以部署和运行Springwood
workloads on those layers I'm gonna use
我要使用的那些层上的工作负载
the examples of Cloud Foundry and and
Cloud Foundry和
kubernetes so speaking of that I know
谈到Kubernetes，我知道
this is not a platform conference who in
这不是一个平台会议，
the room is has ever been been working
房间一直在工作
with cloud foundry so that's a few
与云代工厂，这是几个
who s been working with kubernetes
谁在使用kubernetes
that's a few more I yeah I started
那是我开始的更多
talking about that like one and a half
像一个半的谈论
years ago or something like that then it
年前或类似的东西然后
was quite the opposite way around cubrir
与cubrir完全相反
this was just like in the very beginning
就像一开始一样
but it has a very strong adoption rate
但是它的采用率非常高
and it's it's growing really fast so
而且它的增长非常快，所以
either way if you're not familiar with
无论哪种方式，如果您不熟悉
with either one I'm gonna cover all of
有一个我要覆盖所有
the basics as well to make sure I get
以及确保我得到的基础知识
you all on board so first a little
你们所有人都在船上，所以先一点
disclaimer if you compare those two
如果您比较这两个则免责声明
platforms you can also compare in
您也可以比较的平台
various levels so what I'm not gonna
各个级别，所以我不会
talk about today is pretty much
今天说的差不多
everything beneath container levels so
一切都在容器水平以下
it's not like how many VMs do you need
这不像您需要多少个虚拟机
to install your cluster and what what
安装集群以及什么
I'm gonna be like the difference in
我会喜欢
platform topics and also I'm not gonna
平台主题，我也不会
want to go into like vendor specific
想要像特定于供应商一样进入
implementations so like Google versus
像Google与
Amazon kubernetes or PCF vs. SAPT loud
Amazon Kubernetes或PCF与SAPT对比
foundry or whatsoever I really want to
铸造厂或我真正想要的任何东西
stick to like the open source core and
坚持喜欢开源核心
just show how does how does platforms
只是展示平台如何运作
behave and when you what you basically
表现，当你基本上
expect from them so yeah this is what I
期待他们，是的，这就是我
want to talk about so right here this is
想在这里说的是
like my mrs. or mr. developer with a
像我太太一样或先生开发商与
certain kind of an application I can do
我可以做的某种应用
this no in a generic way today it will
今天没有通用的方式
of course be like a Springwood
当然像斯普林伍德
application and then all the things that
应用程序，然后所有的东西
you face if you want to run this on on a
如果您想在一个
cloud platform so first step basically
云平台，所以第一步基本上
how easy is it to get it deployed what
部署它有多容易
are the steps for me necessary to take
是我必须采取的步骤
to get the application running there how
使应用程序在那里运行
simple is that then once it's running
很简单，那就是一旦运行
what happens if an application crashes
如果应用程序崩溃怎么办
how quickly or how does the platform
平台有多快或如何
recover that and what do I need to do in
恢复那个，我需要做什么
order to to make the platform doing so
为了使平台做到这一点
then scaling is one of the big things in
那么扩大规模是其中的大事之一
in cloud technologies so how easily can
在云技术中如此容易
I scale and what how does the platform
我扩展，平台如何运作
help me with this logging is of course
当然帮我这个日志
very important from a developer
开发者非常重要
perspective so once that was something I
角度，所以一旦那是我的事
was wrong how can I get an insight of
是错误的，我该如何了解
what my application does and service
我的应用程序可以做什么和服务
bindings
绑定
meaning in a way that normally I don't
意思是通常我不会
just push an application code we just
只是推送应用程序代码
had a session in here for neo4j there
在这里有一个针对neo4j的会议
are several other services like back-end
还有其他一些服务，例如后端
services for messaging and databases
消息传递和数据库服务
that you can attach to so how easy or
您可以依附的方式如此简单或
complicated is that and zero downtime
复杂的是停机时间为零
deployment basically meaning if I have a
部署基本上意味着如果我有一个
certain version of the application
特定版本的应用程序
running and I want to deploy a new
正在运行，我想部署一个新的
version is there a possibility to they
版本有可能
have a transition that the end user
过渡到最终用户
would not notice that I have deployed
不会注意到我已经部署
something new so basically in a way that
基本上以某种方式
like Amazon or Facebook that's an all
像Amazon或Facebook一样
the time so your refresh your browser
时间，以便您刷新浏览器
and suddenly something has changed and
突然有些改变了
you get some new content but there's no
您会获得一些新内容，但是没有
obvious downtime or interruption of the
明显的停机时间或
application something which is also
应用的东西也是
relevant in in spring Buddha Lord is
在春季有关的佛陀是
like external configuration so how can I
喜欢外部配置，那我该怎么办
access my Springwood properties how can
访问我的Springwood属性如何
I modify them and change them during the
我修改它们并在
runtime of the application so I got
应用程序的运行时，所以我得到了
roughly 45 minutes to do all that I try
大约45分钟即可完成我尝试的所有操作
to show most of the things live I can't
展示大多数事情，我无法
promise if I can show all of that but
保证我能展示所有这些，但是
let's see how that goes so for those who
让我们来看看那些
have not raised their hands before I
我还没举手
want to just give a brief introduction
只想简单介绍一下
about the two technologies so Cloud
关于这两种技术，所以云
Foundry I mean if you consider spring
铸造我是说如果考虑春天
boot as something that makes it easier
作为更容易启动的东西
to build a spring application that takes
构建一个需要
a lot of stuff away from the developer
开发人员还有很多东西
and make things easier
使事情变得容易
basically Cloud Foundry was initially
基本上Cloud Foundry最初是
thought of like an extension to that to
被认为是对...的扩展
make things also very easy on a cloud on
使事情在云上也非常容易
a platform perspective and then still
平台角度，然后仍然
follow the the 12 factor application
遵循12要素应用
guidelines so you can see there's a
准则，这样您就可以看到
split between applications and services
在应用程序和服务之间划分
and Cloud Foundry will treat those
然后Cloud Foundry将对待那些
applications and services in a different
不同的应用程序和服务
way so on the application side you meant
在应用程序方面，您的意思是这样
to deploy your hopefully stateless
部署您希望无状态的
applications and all of the state full
应用程序和所有状态已满
services like that persistence and
这样的持久性和
messaging and other legacy things will
消息传递和其他遗留事物
be handled as services so once you
被视为服务，因此一旦您
deploy an application the famous command
部署应用程序的著名命令
is called CF push that will basically
称为CF Push，基本上
send your applique
发送贴花
code to the platform and basically after
代码到平台，基本上之后
that this I should basically draw a line
我基本上应该画一条线
so this is basically until here is what
所以这基本上是直到这
the developer really sees everything
开发人员真的看到了一切
below here is what the platform does and
下面是平台的功能，
you don't necessarily see that so
你不一定会那样看
Cloud Foundry will then come up with a
然后，Cloud Foundry将提出一个
so-called build pick which is ten
所谓的构建选择是十
because it's like the runtime for that
因为就像那样的运行时
application so in case of Springwood or
适用于Springwood或
Java this would basically be a JRE and
Java，这基本上是一个JRE，
bundle those two components together and
将这两个组件捆绑在一起，
so called droplet and build a container
所谓的液滴，并建立一个容器
image out of this and this container
此容器中的图像
image will can then be like easily
图像将可以像轻松
started and scaled and so on however the
开始并扩展，依此类推
end user is not gonna be exposed to that
最终用户不会接触到
container technology so it uses
容器技术，因此使用
containers on the inside but it doesn't
里面的容器，但没有
really expose it to the outside then in
真的把它暴露在外面
order to attach the service there is a
为了附加服务，有一个
command called pine service and then you
命令称为pine服务，然后您
basically trade your service and you
基本上可以交易您的服务，而您
call that command and that pine service
调用该命令和那个松树服务
command will then inject the properties
然后命令将注入属性
like for example the JDBC or URL or the
例如JDBC或URL或
credentials into the application so the
凭据进入应用程序，因此
the the the developer does not have to
开发人员不必
configure that manually in the end the
最后手动配置
end-users gonna get a route like a URL
最终用户将获得诸如URL之类的路由
to access the application okay so I mean
可以访问该应用程序，所以我的意思是
this is pretty straightforward
这很简单
any questions that good I mean you you
任何好的问题，我是说你
can of course always interrupt me and
当然可以总是打断我，
and if something is not clear I'm I'm
如果不清楚，我就是
happy to go back a few steps and insert
很高兴回到几步并插入
some more now looking at kubernetes I
现在更多地看我的kubernetes
kind of split this diagram into two
将该图分成两部分
steps because most of you will know that
步骤，因为你们大多数人都知道
you cannot deploy an application
您不能部署应用程序
directly to a plain kubernetes so s
直接到普通的kubernetes这样
Kelsey Hightower like the mr. developer
凯尔西·高塔（Kelsey Hightower）喜欢先生。开发商
advocate of Google for kubernetes says
Google的Kubernetes倡导者说
like the entry ticket to your kubernetes
像您的kubernetes门票
platform is a container and that means
平台是一个容器，这意味着
you have to go to container before you
你必须先去集装箱
can run your code on on kubernetes
可以在kubernetes上运行代码
so this can be done in an easy way like
所以这可以通过简单的方式完成
in a with a docker file where you
在带有docker文件的位置
specify well I have a base image I have
指定得好我有一个基本图像
a runtime and a half an application and
一个运行时半个应用程序，以及
I've run a wrap this all up into a
我把所有东西包起来
container image and that's what a docker
容器映像，这就是码头工人
file will do there are alternative
文件将做替代
options to do that so if they're like
选择这样做，如果他们喜欢
maven ply
专家层
means that will you can attach to your
意味着您可以附加到您的
build process in in Springwood that
在Springwood建立过程
would drop like a container image or
会像容器图像一样下降
there's something from Google called
Google有个东西叫
chip which basically contains crates
基本上包含板条箱的芯片
contain image based on for Java codes
包含基于Java代码的图片
without the necessity to run like a loco
无需像火车头一样奔跑
taco daemon I'm not gonna go into those
塔科守护程序，我不会去那些
I just wanted to make you aware that
我只是想让你知道
this is not the only way to do that
这不是唯一的方法
whatever what is necessary is that you
不管你需要什么
come out with an image and you put that
拿出一张图片，你把
image into an image registry so
映像到映像注册表中
kubernetes can can consume that later on
kubernetes可以在以后使用
that brings us to kubernetes
这使我们进入kubernetes
and this is always a bit more tricky to
而且这总是比较棘手
visualize because it consists a lot of
可视化，因为它包含很多
component now I try to find an
组件现在我尝试找到一个
equivalent to the CF push command which
相当于CF push命令
is Ken it's called like cube CTL run
是Ken，就像多维数据集CTL运行一样
however this command is deprecated it
但是不推荐使用此命令
still works but it's deprecated with the
仍然有效，但已弃用
last version of the CLI so I'm gonna
CLI的最新版本，所以我要
update that in the slide soon anyway
无论如何，请尽快更新幻灯片中的内容
I will demo it this way and it still
我将以这种方式演示它，并且仍然
makes sense to me to use it what that
对我来说使用它是有意义的
this will do is it will do a lot of
这会做很多事情
things I'm gonna start on the under in
我要从下面开始的事情
the low level so the smallest deployable
低级别，因此可部署的最小
unit or handleable units in kubernetes
Kubernetes中的单位或可处理单位
is so-called pot and this is coming from
是所谓的锅，这是从
the animal world where it means like a
在动物世界中意味着
pot can be like a group of whales and
锅就像一群鲸鱼，
you probably all are aware that this
你们可能都知道
like dr. logo is that whale so a pot
像博士徽标是那只鲸鱼，一壶
basically mean one two men technically
从技术上来说基本上是指一两个男人
one two many whales now this definition
一对多鲸现在这个定义
will basically access that image
基本上将访问该图像
registry where you pushed your image
您将图片推送到的注册表
before get the image and start a
在获取图像并开始之前
container instance of that so
这样的容器实例
potentially it can start more than one
可能会启动多个
in image containers in one pot but that
在一个锅中的图像容器中，但是
doesn't always make sense so as I said
如我所说，并不总是很有意义
it's the smallest scalable unit and if
它是最小的可扩展单位，如果
you scale a pot then you scale all the
你缩放锅，然后缩放所有
instances in there and this is something
实例在那里，这是东西
you should be aware when you start
开始时应该注意
because if you start like modeling and
因为如果您开始喜欢建模和
say well I have this like web
说好我有这样的网络
application with like a front end in the
像前端一样的应用程序
back end in a database and I this pot
在数据库的后端，我这个锅
kind of things make sense to me I'm
这类事情对我来说很有意义
gonna prove it all in there it's not a
要证明那一切，这不是一个
good idea because then you basically
好主意，因为那时你基本上
schedule database too
也安排数据库
which is not great so in the end I
不好，所以最后我
normally say if you have a clean
通常说你是否干净
stateless application a one-to-one
一对一的无状态应用程序
mapping of of a container to a pot makes
容器到锅的映射使
makes the most sense if there might be
如果可能的话最有意义
cases where two containers might want to
两个容器可能想要
share something on the underlying file
在基础文件上共享内容
system then it's the time to do that
系统，是时候这样做了
if you group them in the pot kubernetes
如果您将它们分组在锅kubernetes中
will also make sure that all containers
还要确保所有容器
in the ends will run on the same
最终将在相同的
physical node of the cluster so they
集群的物理节点，因此它们
will always be like co-located but if
将始终像在同一地点，但如果
you have like a clean loosely coupled
你就像一个干净的松散耦合
micro-service design this shouldn't
微服务设计，这不应该
matter to you so really if you have the
对你很重要，如果你有
feeling that you want to group more
感觉你想分组更多
containers in one pot then you should
一个锅中的容器，那么你应该
probably question your design now the
现在可能会质疑您的设计
next important object is a so-called
下一个重要对象是所谓的
replica set and as the name says a
副本集，顾名思义，
replica set takes care of about the
副本集负责
replication basically the scaling of
复制基本上是按比例缩放
those pots so this will basically in the
这些锅，所以这基本上会在
end make sure the amount of instances
最后确保实例数量
are running that that the configuration
正在运行该配置
holds and the deployment is that top
持有，部署是最重要的
level object that can pretend should
可以假装的关卡对象
control multiple replica sets so this
控制多个副本集，这样
packet becomes important if you want to
如果您想
roll out a new version of your
推出您的新版本
application either with a new container
带有新容器的应用程序
image or with a new configuration then
图像或使用新配置
it will take care to start that new
它会小心启动新的
replica set start a new pots and make a
副本集开始一个新的花盆，并制作一个
smooth transition so to finally expose
平稳过渡，以便最终暴露
the application to your end view so
应用程序到您的最终视图
there are objects called services and a
有一些对象称为服务，
special object called ingress which
称为入口的特殊对象
basically provides access to the to the
基本上提供了对
to the pots by default if you deploy a
如果您部署一个
port nobody else can access it then the
端口没有其他人可以访问它，然后
port itself the containers in within the
将容器本身移植到
port they can see each other but no one
他们可以看到对方但没有人的港口
else and there are different levels of
否则，有不同程度的
services so you can either say this port
服务，所以您可以说这个港口
can be only visible to other parts in
只能对中的其他部分可见
the cluster this part can be visible too
集群这部分也可见
like somebody who has access to the node
像有权访问该节点的人
or this can be accessed by like a load
或者可以像负载一样访问
balancer from the outside and everybody
外部和所有人的平衡器
can connect sess that that has that IP
可以连接具有该IP的sess
so and in the end you can get that end
所以最终你可以达到目的
point and the user can finally access
点，用户最终可以访问
this so what you can already see from
因此，您已经可以从中看到
those two pay
那两个付出
cheese is a tendency that we will have
奶酪是我们将要拥有的一种趋势
throughout of this talk there is a lot
在整个谈话中，有很多
more things a lot more artifacts in
更多的东西更多的工件
communities that you can tweak and turn
您可以调整和转变的社区
and configure this might be quite useful
并配置它可能非常有用
but that interns also brings along a
但是那个实习生也带来了
necessity to understand what you're
有必要了解你是什么
doing because it well it won't really
之所以这样做，是因为它不会真的
guide you from setting up things wrong
指导您设置错误的地方
okay so before I go into the demo I mean
好吧，所以在我进入演示之前，我的意思是
this is basically the technology stack
这基本上是技术栈
that I'm trying to show I have a spring
我试图表明我有春天
good application and I'll try to use the
好的应用程序，我将尝试使用
same code and and run this on on the
相同的代码，然后在
Cloud Foundry side and in parallel on
Cloud Foundry端并行
like on a dock
就像在码头上
and come on either side so I hope all of
并在任何一侧来，所以我希望所有
this goes right and the network's not
这是正确的，网络不是
gonna let me down so just quickly this
要让我失望，所以很快
is my application in the end I have a
到底是我的申请
simple get mapping which basically
简单地获取映射，基本上
returns the instance ID of the
返回的实例ID
application this is basically the idea
应用这基本上是个主意
of the scaling instance within cloud
云中扩展实例的数量
foundry or kubernetes I use that to
铸造或kubernetes，我用它来
visualize to you if we're running
可视化您是否正在跑步
multiple instances and a load balancer
多个实例和一个负载均衡器
kicks in to basically switch between the
基本上可以在
applications
应用领域
then I added a setting to like get the
然后我添加了一个设置来喜欢
profile this is just like the stay the
个人资料，这就像住宿
active profile and so I'm gonna change
活动资​​料，所以我要更改
this say hola so this is what's my part
这个说呼啦，这就是我的职责
of the life coding today so I've write
今天的生活编码，所以我写
for myself
为了我自己
and then I have an endpoint which just
然后我有一个端点
symbolizes a stupid programmer behavior
象征着愚蠢的程序员行为
it triggers a system exit zero which
它触发系统退出零
causes the de JVM to shut down so this
导致de JVM关闭，因此
is my mini mini version of like chaos
是我的混乱的迷你迷你版
engineering so I think if Benjamin booms
工程，所以我想如果本杰明繁荣
from today would be here he would not
从今天起他就不会在这里
agree with that but I should be enough
同意这一点，但我应该足够
to like symbolize what I want to do here
喜欢象征我想在这里做什么
now I'm I'm trying to run this side by
现在我正在尝试并肩作战
side first of all I've just changed the
首先，我刚刚改变了
code that means I have to rebuild that
代码，这意味着我必须重建
this shouldn't take very long and then
这应该不会花很长时间，然后
though things should be really fairly
虽然事情应该真的很公平
familiar with with most of us this is
与我们大多数人熟悉的是
like a spring conference so and now I'm
就像春季会议一样，现在我
gonna start with on the Cloud Foundry
从Cloud Foundry开始
side and then try to set the thing in
然后尝试将东西放在
parallel with communities so on Cloud
与社区平行，在云上
Foundry you can use like CF push and
可以使用CF推和
then specify the the char file or the
然后指定char文件或
application artifact that you want to
您想要的应用程序工件
you to to push or you can like put this
你去推动，或者你喜欢把它
in a small Yama file where you say okay
在一个小的Yama文件中，您说还可以
this is the the the Charter that I have
这是我的宪章
just built and then I'm gonna set some
刚建成，然后我要设置一些
memory and amount of instances and give
内存和实例数量并给
it a name so all those are optional
它的名字，所以所有这些都是可选的
they Cloud Foundry would also generate
他们Cloud Foundry也会产生
them by by onaga rhythms but in this
他们由onaga节奏，但在这个
case i'm can be a bit sure that that
情况下，我可以确定
this goes well so i'm just gonna check
一切顺利，所以我要检查
if i'm where i'm connected and only have
如果我在我所连接的地方，并且只有
multiple different environments so this
多个不同的环境
looks good
看起来不错
so then I say CF push and it will read
所以我说CF推送，它将显示为
that file and start uploading that code
该文件并开始上传该代码
to the platform and basically identify
到平台并基本确定
the code figure out at some point that
代码在某个时候指出
this is a Java code it will download the
这是一个Java代码，它将下载
build packs and then starts to create
构建包，然后开始创建
that that container that normally takes
通常需要的那个容器
a minute or two so in the meantime we
一两分钟，与此同时，我们
can try to do something similar on on
可以尝试继续做类似的事情
the kubernetes side so as I said I have
kubernetes方面，正如我所说的，
I have just compiled that code so I have
我刚刚编译了该代码，所以我有
the char file and so the next step for
char文件，因此下一步
me but basically to build that container
我，但基本上是建立那个容器
so looking at that docker file this is
所以看那个码头工人文件是
basically what it I mean this could be
基本上我的意思是这可能是
different it's just a sample in the end
不同的只是最后的一个样本
I'm using like an open JDK Alpine base
我正在使用像开放的JDK Alpine基地
image then I create some directory there
图片，然后在其中创建一些目录
I copy that that char file in there and
我在那里复制那个char文件，
I basically tell the the advise stalker
我基本上告诉劝告缠扰者
so once you started this is like the
所以一旦开始，这就像
Java - char is your command to run that
Java-char是运行该命令的命令
container
容器
that means I'm gonna build this I'm
这意味着我要建立这个我
gonna give it a name like version zero
要给它起一个零版本的名字
one and then it's gonna pull the code
一个，然后要拉代码
runs through that steps and then I have
通过这些步骤，然后我有
my container image locally so the next
我的容器映像在本地，所以下一个
step would then be to push this to a
然后将步骤推到
container registry I have some of the
容器注册表我有一些
commands already prepared in the cache
缓存中已准备好的命令
so that will save me some time and if
这样可以节省一些时间，如果
the network is not too slow it's gonna
网络不是太慢，它会
upload that it's like Network the Wi-Fi
上载类似于Wi-Fi网络
seems to be friendly with me today 20
今天好像对我很友善20
Meg is not that much and then things
梅格没那么多事
should be up in my image registry so I'm
应该在我的图像注册表中，所以我
using docker hub as like a public
像公众一样使用docker hub
repository if you run kubernetes locally
如果您在本地运行kubernetes
in your environment I would not
在你的环境中我不会
recommend to push your productive images
建议提高您的形象
to talker hub that would basically mean
到说话者中心，这基本上意味着
you have to set up an own image registry
您必须设置自己的图像注册表
so this one in the meantime has come up
所以与此同时
I called it simple web and if I do like
我称其为简单网络，如果我喜欢
a curl on this simple web yeah you all
在这个简单的网页上卷曲，是的，你们所有人
right yeah so European conference a so
是的，所以欧洲会议如此
um yes so it's gonna say this is my ID
嗯，所以这是我的身份证
the profile that I activated is Steph
我激活的个人资料是Steph
because that's the before profile that I
因为那是我之前的个人资料
said and it says hola Barcelona so if I
说，它说呼啦巴塞罗那，所以如果我
I can now put this into like a while
我现在可以将其放入一段时间
loop and then yeah it pings it
循环然后对它进行ping操作
continuously so I I have a very big
不断，所以我有一个很大的
screen resolution is I might changed it
屏幕分辨率我可能会改变
a little bit so sorry I was pressing the
有点抱歉，我按了
wrong key okay so this is basically
密码错误，好吧，这基本上是
doing a thing and I'll try to split the
做某事，我将尝试拆分
screen and put a watch command in here
屏幕并在此处放置监视命令
so I can say now watch CF app simple web
所以我可以说现在观看CF应用程序简单的网络
and this should now tell me something
现在这应该告诉我一些事情
that this app is running so I'm also
该应用程序正在运行，所以我也
gonna make this a little smaller
会使它变小
is this still kind of readable well in
这在
the background okay I mean I can't say
背景还可以，我不能说
come up to the front because the front
出现在前面，因为前面
is pretty much blocked already now as I
现在我已经被封锁了
said this is running and doing it thing
说这正在运行并正在做的事情
should look a little different anyway
无论如何应该看起来有点不同
what I wanted to do of course is now
我现在想做的就是
play the chaos monkey and say okay this
扮演混乱的猴子，说好吧
is the URL and invoke that fail command
是URL并调用该fail命令
so now that means the application will
所以现在这意味着应用程序将
crash and it says okay it can't resolve
崩溃，它说好了，它无法解决
the request I can also see here in a
该请求我也可以在这里看到
second or so it refreshed every two
每秒钟大约刷新一次
seconds
秒
that's this application went down it now
那就是这个应用程序现在被关闭了
went into starting mode again and after
再次进入启动模式
a couple of seconds like now the
像现在这样几秒钟
application is coming back so this is my
应用程序回来了，所以这是我的
basic one on one thing on a cloud
基本一对一
platform that I would basically expect
我基本上会期望的平台
what else I can do that I said before so
我之前说过的我还能做些什么
I can also scale the application call it
我也可以扩展应用程序调用它
three instances and then the it will
三个实例，然后它将
spin up to new ones so two new ones are
升级到新的，所以有两个新的
starting and as soon as the build peg
开始并尽快建立钉
will detect that the Java process come
将检测到Java进程来了
up has come up successfully it will put
up up成功了，它将把
them into the load balancer and you can
将它们放入负载均衡器中，您可以
see that now by basically by those
现在基本上由那些人看到
alternating IDs that that it balances
平衡的备用ID
the load between those applications so
这些应用程序之间的负载
that's what to two simple commands not
这是两个简单命令所不具备的
too difficult for me and now I can also
对我来说太难了，现在我也可以
do like this curl command again for it
再次喜欢这个curl命令
like to file an application and it you
想提交申请，而您
will see now that this one is starting
现在将看到这是一个开始
so Cloud Foundry has detected that and
因此Cloud Foundry已检测到
it it's immediately isolated this one
它马上被隔离了
from from the load balancing mechanism
来自负载平衡机制
so the end what the end user sees is
所以最终用户看到的是
that they would never realized that
他们永远不会意识到
there is an outage I can do that of
有停电我可以做到的
course again and as this is so much fun
再来一次，因为这很有趣
I can do it again
我可以再做一次
and maybe again and sooner or later
也许再迟早
well it's it recovers quite quickly
好吧，它恢复得很快
normally it should say it should be
通常应该说应该是
possible to get it interested okay now I
有可能让它感兴趣好吧我
have crashing a couple of times and it
崩溃了几次，它
might get angry with me but still you
可能会生我的气，但你仍然
can see what this platform kind of
可以看到这个平台是什么样的
provides as a resilience mechanism to
提供作为恢复机制
say it's such a failing component now I
说这是一个失败的组成部分
want to try to reproduce the same thing
想尝试重现同一件事
in in combinators so I also want to
在组合器中，所以我也想
split my screen and show you something
分割我的屏幕并显示一些内容
so I'm gonna say watch cube CTL get and
所以我要说看多维数据集CTL
now all the objects that I talked about
现在我谈论的所有对象
before deployment replica set pod and
在部署副本之前设置pod和
services so if I do this now there's
服务，所以如果我现在这样做，
only a single like built-in service that
只有一个类似的内置服务
kubernetes provides itself so this is
kubernetes提供了自己，所以这是
nothing that comes from my side and I
我身边没有任何东西
have pushed the image now so I can say
现在已经推送了图像，所以我可以说
cube CTL run and I say simple web with
立方体CTL运行，我说简单的网站
one replicas to start with I reference
一个副本以我参考开始
my image and I pass a environment
我的形象，我经过一个环境
variable to basically specify the active
基本指定活动变量
spring profile so if I do that it will
春天的轮廓，所以如果我这样做，它将
tell me here it's deprecated but I'm not
告诉我这里已弃用，但我不是
gonna care about this now I want to care
现在要关心这个我要关心
more on what's happening here so as you
更多关于这里发生的事情，以便您
can see a couple of things happened so
可以看到发生了几件事
I've created a deployment object under
我已经在下面创建了一个部署对象
that the curator replica set and it
策展人副本集及其
started with one pot because I basically
一锅开始，因为我基本上
said please do that with with one
说请与一个
instance so if I want to try the same
实例，所以如果我想尝试相同的
thing I mean this one okay no this will
我的意思是，这个可以，不可以
not work yet yeah I forgot what I need
还没工作，是的，我忘了我需要的东西
to do of course is it's expose this
要做的当然是暴露这个
component as a service so I'm going to
组件即服务，因此我将
say use take this deployment simple web
说使用此部署简单的网站
and expose this as a service of type
并将其公开为类型的服务
load balancer this is like the exposing
负载均衡器这就像暴露
it via external IP and include a load
通过外部IP并包含负载
balancer on that and when I do that I'm
平衡器，当我这样做时，
getting bit of problems with mirrors
镜子有点问题
the resolution here so you can make it a
这里的分辨率，因此您可以将其
little smaller so this service has now
小一点，所以这项服务现在
just got created and the external IP of
刚创建，并且的外部IP
that is localhost so if I curl localhost
那是本地主机，所以如果我卷曲本地主机
now it should basically come back with
现在基本上应该回来了
the same thing so this is the same
同一件事，所以这是相同的
Springwood application now running
Springwood应用程序现在正在运行
inside a docker container inside of
在docker容器内
kubernetes and doing the same thing so I
kubernetes并做同样的事情，所以我
will just repeat what I have done before
只会重复我之前所做的
to show you how this looks basically on
告诉你这基本上看起来如何
the other sides problem with my Mac
Mac的另一面问题
keyboard at the moment so no this is not
目前没有键盘，这不是
hello I've used different versions of
你好，我用过不同版本的
this application as you can see from my
您可以从我的应用程序中看到
so this is working now and it basically
所以这现在正在工作，基本上
does it in a very similar way so it
这样做的方式非常相似
pings it every second and checks if the
每秒对其进行ping操作，并检查是否
application is behaving fine so if I do
应用程序运行正常，所以如果我这样做
the same thing here and say localhost
同样的事情在这里说本地主机
and fail it will then kill the
并失败，它将杀死
application you can probably see this in
应用程序，您可能会在
a second right here that it basically
这里的第二个权利
goes from a running into like a first
从奔跑变成了第一个
completed and then again into a running
完成后再进入运行状态
state and now it comes back so same
状态，现在又回来了
thing pretty much same timing I mean I
事情几乎是同一时间，我是说我
should probably say I'm running
应该说我在跑步
kubernetes locally on a docker for Mac
Mac版docker上的本地kubernetes
instance and the cloud foundry is public
实例和云铸造厂是公共的
so I'm not really comparing apples to
所以我不是真的比较苹果
apples here but it's about the same
苹果在这里，但是差不多
similar response time now if I if I want
如果我愿意的话，现在的响应时间也差不多
to scale in communities I can this would
在社区扩大规模，我可以做到这一点
be the command to say I'm on so many
可以说我有很多
replicas and the deployment of simple
复制品和简单部署
web and now I get two additional ports
网络，现在我有两个附加端口
so it penetrates the containers and now
所以它穿透了容器，现在
you can see a couple of things on this
您可以在此看到几件事
side so even though I had a healthy
即使我身体健康
instance running and I scale two more
实例正在运行，我又扩展了两个
instances my end user will see an outage
我的最终用户将遇到中断的情况
and this is by kind of very fundamental
这是非常基本的
to the understanding between application
对应用程序之间的理解
and containers it's like kubernetes is
和容器，就像kubernetes是
basically only aware about if a
基本上只知道如果
container is running or not so when it
容器是否正在运行
starts the container and the
启动容器，然后
process of the container is there and
容器的过程在那里
then the load balancer by default will
那么默认情况下，负载均衡器将
route the traffic to that container but
将流量路由到该容器，但
at that point the Springwood application
那时，Springwood应用程序
within the container is not ready yet so
容器中的容器尚未准备好
this is something that you need to
这是你需要做的
configure additionally I have prepared
配置我已经准备好了
that it just needs you against me some
只需要你反对我一些
better so I have I have a cheat sheet
更好，所以我有备忘单
because I'm not young I'll save all time
因为我还不年轻，所以我会节省所有时间
and this component is called the
这个组件称为
readiness probe as you can see here
您可以在这里看到准备就绪探针
which you have to add to your kubernetes
您必须将其添加到kubernetes
configure 8 come on
配置8加油
so I'm gonna take this out and then to
所以我要把这个拿出来然后
edit a deployment or basically any
编辑部署或基本上任何一个
module in kubernetes you can just
您可以在kubernetes中使用模块
basically type cube CTL edit and then
基本上键入多维数据集CTL编辑，然后
deployment simple web and that basically
部署简单的网络，基本上
brings you to that llamo notation of the
带您到llamo符号的
overall configuration and if you are a
整体配置，如果您是
fan of llamo then kubernetes is tell me
llamo的粉丝然后kubernetes告诉我
the right place for you so there's a lot
最适合您的地方，所以有很多
and so this is the specification that we
这就是我们的规范
deployed before so you can see here
之前已部署，因此您可以在此处看到
that's like the active spring profile
就像活跃的弹簧轮廓
with the value of Def this is my image
与Def的价值，这是我的形象
and so on and right now I'm just gonna
等等，现在我要
edit this readiness probe into it the
编辑此准备情况探针
only thing I should change is that
我唯一应该改变的是
endpoint because it's not called hello
终结点，因为它不叫你好
it's just called this leave the base
这就是所谓的离开基地
that was so and what will happen now I
是这样，现在会发生什么
need to be quick so no it created a new
需要快速，所以没有它创造了一个新的
replica set because I have changed the
副本集，因为我更改了
configuration and what its gonna do now
配置及其现在将要做什么
it's gonna start the new part in a new
它将开始新的新部分
replica set and once this is healthy it
复制集，一旦运行良好，
will take down the old one you can see
会取下你可以看到的旧的
now it's running but it's not ready so
现在它正在运行，但是还没有准备好，所以
the container is there but the
容器在那里，但是
Springwood application is not and only
Springwood的应用程序不是唯一的
once this will come up successfully and
一旦成功，
criminate is able to ping the point the
criminate能够发现问题
endpoint then it's gonna start taking
终结点，那么它将开始服用
down the other ones so this is something
下来其他的，所以这是东西
what the Cloud Foundry build peg will
Cloud Foundry的构建钉将如何
provide you out of the box in kubernetes
在kubernetes中为您提供开箱即用的功能
you have to configure it manually still
您仍然必须手动配置
I mean you can achieve the same thing
我的意思是你可以实现同样的目标
I need to have a look on the time you
我要看看你的时间
know I guess negative time left right so
知道我猜是负的时间，所以
we've done that and now another thing
我们已经做到了，现在另一件事
that I wanted to show quickly is it's
我想快速展示的是
the logging of that so in Cloud Foundry
在Cloud Foundry中进行记录
it's like CF logs and then the name of
就像CF日志，然后是
the application and it has a built in
该应用程序，它具有内置的
logging aggregator so what you're
日志聚合器，所以您是
basically going to see here is the the
基本上要在这里看到的是
ongoing log of all the applications and
所有应用程序的持续日志
in here you can basically if you read it
在这里你基本上可以阅读
somewhat correctly you see the instance
在某种程度上您看到了实例
ID and things as well because it's
ID和其他东西，因为它是
constantly pinged but it will
不断ping但它会
continuously log and aggregate the logs
连续记录并汇总日志
over all the instance of a certain
在某个特定情况下
application type now on community side
现在在社区方面的应用程序类型
lot the logging works in a similar way
很多日志以类似的方式工作
you have cube CTL locks but in this case
您具有多维数据集CTL锁，但在这种情况下
you need to specify the ID of the pot so
您需要指定锅的ID，以便
you have to identify the pot ID and and
您必须确定底池ID和
only then you can do like a continuous
只有这样你才能做一个连续的
log so now it's basically this is like
登录，所以现在基本上这就像
the end of the of the of the spring
春天的结束
boots would process so it's it's
靴子会处理，所以
standing right now not doing nothing not
现在站着不做任何事都不做
doing anything else one of the things
做其他事情之一
that don't like I mean first of all it's
不喜欢我的意思是首先
kind of cumbersome that I have to pick
我必须挑的那种麻烦
out the the pot ID the other thing is I
拿出锅ID，另一件事是我
could basically lock it gives me the
基本上可以锁定它给我
option to log on a level of labels so
选择登录级别的标签，以便
I'm not gonna go very deep into labels
我不会深入标签
but this one has a label run simple web
但是这个有一个标签可以运行简单的网页
so if I do that it will basically
所以如果我这样做，基本上
collect the locks over all three of the
收集所有三个的锁
or basically over all of the deployed
或基本上覆盖了所有已部署的
instances but for some reason that I
实例，但由于某种原因我
have never figured out why I can't let
从来没有想过为什么我不能让
this one run continuously so I can
这个连续运行，所以我可以
either label or run the locks
标签或运行锁
continuously that means if you want to
连续地意味着如果你想
do achieved the same thing you have as
确实取得了与您相同的成就
in Cloud Foundry you probably have to
在Cloud Foundry中，您可能必须
take an additional tooling to do that
采取额外的工具来做到这一点
so what else did I want to show ya
所以我还想告诉你
patching now now we've discovered this
现在修补，我们发现了这个
that we have a code which is kind of
我们有一个这样的代码
buggy fortunately we have two
幸运的是，我们有两个
Abell platforms that provide resilience
提供弹性的Abell平台
to cope with that in the end I mean if
最后要解决这个问题
it's not only me pinging that point like
不仅是我这样敲击
on a curl command but there's usually
在curl命令上，但是通常
going on to that it shouldn't be it
继续说那不应该是这样
shouldn't be like that so I'm gonna
不应该那样，所以我要
update my codes so this is part two of
更新我的代码，所以这是第二部分
my life coding and I'm gonna specify
我的生活编码，我要说明
this like a new version of the
这就像新版本的
application now and I'm gonna take this
现在申请，我要接受这个
bad call out so that's that and then I'm
不好的喊出来就是这样，然后我
pregnant in a new window
在新窗口中怀孕
I'm gonna build a new a new Chara file
我要建立一个新的新Chara文件
so this has basically the the patched
所以这基本上是补丁
code now yes this looks fine I mean it
代码现在是的，这看起来很好，我是说真的
doesn't of course pick it up
当然不接
automatically but they're commands to
自动，但它们是命令
deal with that now in Cloud Foundry the
现在在Cloud Foundry中处理
on a naked Cloud Foundry you would have
在裸露的Cloud Foundry上，您将拥有
to apply a manual Bluegreen deployment
应用手动Bluegreen部署
so you basically pushed a new code and
所以你基本上推了一个新的代码，
once this is tested and running fine you
一旦测试通过并运行良好
switch like the route tool into the new
像路线工具一样切换到新
application and you have a smooth
应用程序，你会很顺利
transition then there are command-line
过渡，然后有命令行
plugins one that I'm using here now
我现在在这里使用的插件
which is called blue-green deploy which
这称为蓝绿色部署
does that automatically for you so in
为您自动执行此操作
the end it will I'm gonna can also show
最后我将要展示的是
this here it will create a new
这将在这里创建一个新的
application and call this simple web new
应用程序并将其称为新的简单网络
and then basically wait until this
然后基本上等到
application is up and ready in order to
应用程序已准备就绪，以便
to start using it and now once that's
开始使用它，现在一旦
there and well this request aside is not
在那里，好吧，这个要求不是
entirely correct because this one is
完全正确，因为这是
still working and this reports already
仍在工作，该报告已经
started so it's a little too optimistic
开始，所以有点太乐观了
but I'm very confident that it's gonna
但我非常有信心
make it in the end
最终做到
so once this app will become ready
所以一旦这个程序准备就绪
is always the seconds that feels like
总是像
hours on a live presentation guess most
现场演示的几个小时猜对最多
if you have seen that before I'm I
如果你在我之前就已经看到了
should have probably scaled it down to
应该把它缩小到
one but it's not still gonna work so now
一个，但仍然无法正常工作，所以现在
the new one is there and now it's gonna
新的在那里，现在它将
do that switch and changing that routes
进行切换并更改路线
and at the old route to the new
并在旧路线到新路线
application and at one point it will
应用程序，它会在某一时刻
just come back with the version two so
刚带着第二版回来了
it takes the old instances out if if I
如果我将旧实例删除
have only one instance it's more
只有一个实例就更多了
impressive because then you have like a
令人印象深刻，因为那时你就像一个
switch from one HTTP call to the next
从一个HTTP调用切换到下一个
one the bottom line is your end user is
最重要的是您的最终用户是
never gonna notice so this is the way
永远不会注意到，所以这就是方法
how you can basically patch application
基本上如何修补应用程序
code still maintain all rest points to
代码仍然保留所有休息点
be to be alive and if I had not added
要活着，如果我没有添加
that version two I don't think anybody
那第二版我不认为有人
would have would have would have really
本来会本来真的
seen this so and if I do like to prove
看到了这一点，如果我想证明
that so if I invoke that failed command
这样，如果我调用该失败的命令
it says now fixed so this code has been
它说现在已修复，因此此代码已
patched and it's not the application is
补丁，不是应用程序
not vulnerable anymore now on kubernetes
现在在kubernetes上不再脆弱
sites you might guess it Yui gonna deal
您可能会猜到的网站Yui会成交
with a similar thing so the first thing
与类似的事情，所以第一件事
we're gonna do is build a new container
我们要做的是建立一个新的容器
image and the next one will be to to
图片，下一个将是
push that image
推那个形象
so ten more minutes
再等十分钟
that's that should be working
那应该是可行的
I'm gonna take a photo in the meantime
同时我要拍张照片
I've never seen I've never had such a
我从未见过我从未有过这样的经历
big crowd where people have were sitting
人们坐在那里的大人群
on the floor I'm really I need to send
在地板上，我真的需要发送
this to my manager anyways raising your
反正这给我的经理
hands real quick and if you find that
快速动手，如果您发现
cool okay awesome
酷好吧真棒
thank you very much this is I'm gonna
非常感谢你，我要
have a very happy evening today now okay
今天过一个快乐的夜晚，好吗
this is done we we can go back to this
这完成了，我们可以回到这个
so in here we have to do the the similar
所以在这里我们必须做类似的
thing as before and say cube CTL edit
和以前一样，说多维数据集CTL编辑
deployment simple web and so now what I
部署简单的网络，所以我现在
have to do is basically update the name
要做的基本上是更新名称
of that image so I've changed this from
该图像的位置，因此我将其更改为
version zero one two zero two and I'll
版本零一二零二，我会
just demonstrate you if I could do a
只是向你展示我是否可以
stupid type or something like that
愚蠢的类型或类似的东西
not the behavior of the robustness of
不是行为的健壮性
communities so basically submit an image
社区因此基本上提交图像
that it will not be able to find and
它将无法找到和
then it creates a new replica set but it
然后创建一个新的副本集，但是
comes with opponent says it can't pull
对手说不能拉
that image so it doesn't switch to the
该图像，因此它不会切换到
broken image it leaves the old one
残破的图像留下了旧的
running until this will be resolved so
一直运行到解决为止
it does it's it's kind of intelligent
是的，这是一种聪明
there that it doesn't really switch to
那里并没有真正切换到
something which it already knows will be
它已经知道的东西将会是
broken in the end if I do this now so
如果我现在这样做，最终会破裂
now I can an additional replica set so
现在我可以再设置一个副本
we have plenty of replica sets now you
现在我们有很多副本集
can remove them from time to time if you
可以不时删除它们
know they are not relevant anymore
知道他们不再重要了
and here you can see the same thing so
在这里你可以看到同样的东西
now it has switched as we have three
现在它已经切换，因为我们有三个
instances it's still the load bans it
实例仍然是负载禁止它
has to take the other ones down but the
必须取下其他的，但是
Refresh also works here and the new
刷新在这里也适用，新的
version comes in in a very smooth
版本进来非常顺利
transition so this is mostly it from the
过渡，所以这主要是因为
from the live demo site to like go back
从现场演示站点喜欢返回
to the presentation and I hope you all
演讲，我希望大家
this was kind of new to some of you to
这对你们中的某些人来说是新的
other people not really so much in the
其他人不是那么多
platform space so I've seen people
平台空间，所以我见过人们
coming from Cloud Foundry and going to
从Cloud Foundry转到
the kubernetes and vice versa and so the
kubernetes，反之亦然，所以
thing that you can see is like of course
你可以看到的东西当然是
in communities you can configure a lot
在社区中，您可以配置很多
more but you also need to know more
更多，但您还需要了解更多
to prevent you from doing things wrong
防止你做错事
now if you come from kubernetes it looks
现在，如果您来自kubernetes，它看起来
like well this is very simple but can it
很好，这很简单，但是可以吗
do everything that I want to do and so
做我想做的一切，所以
I've listed a couple of things that I
我列出了几件事
really like so especially that life
非常喜欢生活
editing in in communities of the
在社区中编辑
conflict with that built in sirens and
与内置警报器冲突，并且
deployment is really a lot of fun so
部署真的很有趣，所以
that that's that seems to be very well
那似乎很好
thought through and easily usable it has
经过仔细考虑并易于使用
a large functional scope I pretty much
我的功能范围很大
only scratch the surface given the time
给定时间只刮擦表面
and has very granular patterns there so
那里有非常细致的图案
you have different levels of service
您有不同的服务水平
exposure this is what I would actually
曝光这就是我实际上
say from a container scheduling
从集装箱调度中说
perspective is quite an advantage over
相比而言，透视是一个优势
Cloud Foundry if I can say well this one
如果我能说清楚的话，Cloud Foundry
is only visible to others but not to the
仅对其他人可见，而对其他人不可见
outside it's also very good work for
外面的工作也很好
security purposes and the core of
安全目的和核心
communities is very robust and resilient
社区非常强大且富有弹性
I mean this coming out of Google was
我的意思是，这是从Google传来的
their internal system and of course high
他们的内部系统，当然很高
popularity I mean if you look at the CN
人气，我的意思是，如果您看CN
CF ecosystem there are thousands of
CF生态系统有成千上万
products a big because there was oh s s
产品很大，因为那里哦
community and it's pretty much available
社区，几乎可用
everywhere even an Amazon so it's
到处都是亚马逊，所以
definitely something that we have to
绝对是我们必须要做的事情
consider now on the down sides and we've
现在考虑不利的一面，我们已经
seen that a lot in in our projects
在我们的项目中看到很多
especially when we when we migrated from
特别是当我们从
Cloud Foundry that it suddenly became
突然变成了Cloud Foundry
visible developers will need an
可见的开发人员将需要
additional level of skill to properly
适当的其他技能水平
handle containers I mean this is not so
处理容器我不是这样
difficult but to properly handle
困难但要妥善处理
kubernetes because it's it's easy to do
kubernetes，因为它很容易做到
things wrong and it takes about time to
出现问题，这需要时间
find out that things are wrong and the
找出错误的地方，
real the biggest difference really is
真正最大的不同是
that container handling I mean this was
该容器处理，我的意思是
pretty straightforward in my demo now
现在在我的演示中非常简单
like build a container and push the
例如建立一个容器并推动
container in reality you have to do the
容器实际上你必须做
same thing but you also have to maintain
同样的事情，但你也必须保持
them so if a container has a
他们，所以如果一个容器有一个
vulnerability you need to patch it in
您需要修补的漏洞
Cloud Foundry this will be done under
Cloud Foundry将在
the cover but when they exchange the
封面，但当他们交换
base image and also you have to maintain
基本映像，您还必须维护
that registry which will become a new
该注册表将成为一个新的
single point of failure we had one
单点故障，我们只有一个
project where we had the container
我们有容器的项目
registry with a certificate issue
注册表与证书问题
for a couple of weeks so you nothing's
几个星期，所以你什么都不是
gonna happen then because you can't
然后会发生，因为你不能
deploy if you don't have your images so
如果没有图像，请进行部署
this is something you should know
这是你应该知道的
deactivated logging today was basically
今天停用的记录基本上是
just symbolizing that it has a good core
只是象征着它有一个很好的核心
but it often requires more to do so if
但如果这样做，通常需要做更多的工作
you do kubernetes you would probably
你做kubernetes
very soon do like helm for packaging sto
很快就喜欢掌舵包装
Prometheus and a lot of things to attach
普罗米修斯和很多东西要附加
to your system and that means additional
到您的系统，这意味着附加
maintenance of your of your cluster
维护您的集群
infrastructure on the Cloud Foundry site
Cloud Foundry站点上的基础架构
the simple part is really it is very
简单的部分是真的
simple also it has that feeling of being
简单也有那种被
container less so I mean serverless is a
容器更少，所以我的意思是无服务器是一个
very popular term nowadays I'm not a big
如今我很受欢迎
fan of it I'm fan of the technology but
我是技术迷，但是
not of the term because it kind of if it
不是这个词，因为如果
means you don't have to worry about your
意味着您不必担心自己的
server and your infrastructure then it
服务器和您的基础架构
means in cloud phone you don't have to
意味着在云电话中，您不必
worry about containers it's there there
担心容器在那里
they be used they will be used but you
他们会被使用，但会被您使用
don't have to interact with them and in
不必与他们互动
terms of developer productivity you have
您拥有的开发人员生产力条件
a really fast application to to platform
真正快速的平台应用
path and it's very mature so it's been
路径，它已经很成熟了
around a lot longer and then kubernetes
大约更长的时间，然后是kubernetes
is and it just works so it has reduced
是的，它只是工作，所以它减少了
configuration product possibility sorry
配置产品的可能性对不起
possibilities on the downside the
缺点的可能性
blue-green deployment and automatic
蓝绿色部署和自动
patching is not I mean it has the same
修补不是我意思是相同的
functionality but it doesn't seem to be
功能，但似乎不是
as built in as it is in kubernetes
在kubernetes中内置
the problem is it's kind of boring I
问题是我有点无聊
mean last year I visited both Cube cons
意思是去年我参观了两个Cube缺点
I like to queue cons and to Cloud
我喜欢排队不利条件并前往云端
Foundry summits and as this has there's
铸造峰会
not nothing new anymore it's more like
不再没有新的东西了
customer adoptions stories but it's not
客户采用的故事，但事实并非如此
so like new features here and there and
就像在这里和那里的新功能一样
you do new things in the ecosystem it
你在生态系统中做新的事情
it's there and it's and it's set whereas
它在那里，它已经被设置，而
in on the cube con I don't know if
在立方体的骗子我不知道
anyone if you've been there the next one
任何人，如果你去过那里下一个
is happening next week also here in
下周也要发生在这里
Barcelona it's like very enthusiastic
巴塞罗那非常热情
crowd around crowd around that and
拥挤的人群
everybody is presenting their Yama files
每个人都在展示他们的Yama文件
and what they all did with it so it's a
他们都做了什么，所以这是一个
lot of things gonna happen there yeah
那里会发生很多事情
for me it was always on one chord I
对我来说，我总是和弦
wanted to bring in from
想从
Kelsey Hightower and he's like the
凯尔西·高塔（Kelsey Hightower），他就像
number-one advocate for kubernetes is
kubernetes的第一倡导者是
saying it's like it's an infrastructure
就像是基础设施
framework it's yama based but for from
基于yama的框架，但来自
developer perspective it's far away from
开发人员的观点
the productivity you can find in parts
您可以在零件中找到的生产率
of fast platforms and i and it can only
快速平台和我，它只能
like second on that this this is what
像第二一样，这就是
was my experience as well so in the past
过去也是我的经历
this was always my my last slide where I
这永远是我最后一张幻灯片
said like I would like to have a
说我想有一个
platform which has the simplicity of
简单的平台
Cloud Foundry and and the function of
Cloud Foundry及其功能
scope of kubernetes
kubernetes的范围
now this is something that has started
现在这已经开始
growing in the Cloud Foundry community
在Cloud Foundry社区中成长
they have various options for dealing
他们有各种各样的选择
with kubernetes I mean the first one was
使用kubernetes，我的意思是第一个是
the Cloud Foundry container runtime
Cloud Foundry容器运行时
which is a kubernetes full-blown
这是一个成熟的kubernetes
communities and then you run it side by
社区，然后您将其并行运行
side the like pivotal container service
像枢轴式集装箱服务
is like a commercial implementation of
就像是
that then there's quarks which used to
然后有夸克过去
be CF containerization which runs Cloud
运行CF的CF容器化
Foundry in containers provided by
铸造厂提供的容器
kubernetes so that means you already
kubernetes，这意味着您已经
have both platforms inside of each other
两个平台相互内在
and the the most interesting one is the
最有趣的是
so called the project ireenie because as
所谓的项目ireenie是因为
you might have guessed Cloud Foundry as
您可能已经猜到Cloud Foundry为
it existed prior to communities already
它已经存在于社区之前
had an internal container scheduler
有一个内部容器调度程序
otherwise all that functionality would
否则所有这些功能
not be possible now with ireenie
ireenie现在不可能
the idea is to make this pluggable so
这个想法是使它可插拔
the internal name of the Cloud Foundry
Cloud Foundry的内部名称
scheduler is called Diego and the
调度程序称为Diego，
container phone is called garden this
集装箱电话叫花园
was also there prior to docker and now
在docker之前也在那里
the idea is just like to make this
这个想法就像使
configurable so you can say I would
可配置的，所以你可以说我会
rather use kubernetes as the container
而不是使用kubernetes作为容器
engine and use Cloud Foundry as a
引擎并将Cloud Foundry用作
top-level API so this is and I don't
顶级API，所以我不是
expect anybody to know and understand
希望任何人都知道和理解
that the architectural diagram of of
的架构图
cloud foundry inside and you see like
里面有云铸造厂，您会看到
the big portion here is that llego cell
这里最大的部分是非法细胞
which runs all those little containers
运行所有这些小容器
were the workload is in and the ia the
是在工作量和IA
idea for that is just like to use
这个想法就像使用
kubernetes for exactly that and then
kubernetes就是这样，然后
this project ireenie builds like a layer
这个项目ireenie像一层一样
and so from an from an developer side
所以从开发者的角度来看
you have the same API
你有相同的API
but then you go against a kubernetes
但是你反对kubernetes
cluster and that means you can also
集群，这意味着您还可以
access it in that way and interact with
以这种方式访问​​并与之交互
it through kubernetes api or Cloud
通过kubernetes api或Cloud
Foundry API so this is fairly new it was
Foundry API，所以这是相当新的
demoed live on the CF Summoner a couple
在CF Summoner上进行了现场降级
of weeks ago for next year I plan to
几周前的明年，我打算
bring a demo here ok
演示在这里好
so I'm running out of time two more
所以我要再用两个时间
minutes again if you want to reproduce
分钟，如果您想复制
that I have this code repository here on
我在这里有此代码存储库
my github account with all the
我所有的github帐户
instruction steps if you want to get
如果您想获得指导步骤
your hands on to that and play with it
你把手放在那并玩
by yourself for all the people southern
自己为南方人民
Germany yes this is again the hint for
德国是的，这再次是暗示
the Cloud Foundry meetup we definitely
我们肯定会参加Cloud Foundry聚会
don't only talk about Cloud Foundry all
不要只谈论Cloud Foundry
the time because like it's CF push and
时间，因为像CF推和
bind service so it doesn't really
绑定服务，所以它不是真的
require a meetup to talk about that all
需要聚会来谈论这一切
the time and then this is this is a my
时间，然后这是我的
Twitter handle if you a quick
Twitter处理，如果您快速
advertisement this is my colleague
广告这是我的同事
andreas he is currently running a
安德烈亚斯（Andreas）目前正在跑步
security workshop in another room he's
他在另一个房间里的安全车间
gonna have a session on spring clouds on
将会在春天的云上举行会议
kubernetes tomorrow I think at 6:00 in
kubernetes明天我想在6:00
the auditorium so this is a more
礼堂，这是一个更多
advanced level for what I started today
我今天开始的高级水平
as an introduction and yeah feel free to
作为介绍，是的，随时
stop by and game over I see that ok well
停下来玩游戏我很好
thank you
谢谢
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]